telewizjada.net 2015-02-24

# Telewizjada.net - Privacy policy

My Company. ("Company") Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to the Company. We've developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. This Privacy Policy governs your use of the Company web site www.telewizjada.net, and all associated sites linked to www.telewizjada.net by the Company, its agents and affiliates, including Company sites around the world (collectively, "Site") and all other services provided to you by the Company (collectively, "Service"). The terms "you," "your," and "user" refer to the user of our Service. The terms "My Company.," "we," "us," and "our" refer to the Company. By using the Service, you consent to the data practices prescribed in this statement. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Service following the posting of changes will mean that you accept and agree to the changes.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

You may be asked to provide your personal information anytime you use the Service or in contact with the Company or our affiliates. The Company and its affiliates may share this personal information with each other and use it consistent with this Privacy Policy. Here are some examples of the types of personal information the Company may collect and how we may use it.

**What personal information we collect**

When you register a Company account, register your products, purchase a product, download a software update, participate in an online contest, communicate with us through email or phone, or otherwise use our Service, we may collect a variety of information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, device, location, age and occupation.

**How we use your personal information**

The personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on Company's latest product announcements, software updates, and upcoming events.

We also use personal information to help us develop, deliver, and improve our products, services, content, and advertising.

We may also use the information that you provide to respond to your requests, support your use of the Company's products and services, or customize future shopping for you.

From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as changes to our terms, conditions, and policies.

We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve Company's products, services, and customer communications.

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our Service. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary. If you participate, we will request certain personal information from you and we may use the information you provide to administer those programs.

**Cookies and Other Technologies**

The Company and our affiliates may use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons, and other technologies while providing the Service. When you access the Company Service, we may obtain and store certain types of information such as your IP address, time and date of access, language use, the type of browser used and the page(s) you request. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our Service people have used, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements.

If you want to disable cookies, you can do so by modifying the browser settings. Check with your browser provider to find out how to disable cookies. Please note that certain features of the Company Service will not be available once cookies are disabled.

**Information That is Publicly Available**

When you create Company account and use the Company Service, some information about your Company account and your account activity may be provided to other users of the Service. This may include the date and time you opened your account, the date and time you last logged into your account, and the number of messages you have posted to the forum.

Your Company forum nickname, not your email address, is displayed to other users when you engage in certain activities on Company Site, such as when you post messages to Company forum. Other users can contact you by leaving a message or comment on the forum.

Any image, text and information that you submit to the Company Site may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. You are responsible for the information you choose to submit to the Site in these instances.

**Disclosure to Third Parties**

At times the Company may make certain personal information available to third-party affiliates that work with Company to provide products and services, or that help Company market to customers. Personal information will only be shared by the Company to provide or improve our products, services and advertising; it will not be shared with third parties for their marketing purposes. You may request to not having your information submitted to such affiliates by contacting the Company Support here The Company will not sell, lease, share or otherwise use your personal information except as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

The Company may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary: (1) to comply with any law, legal process, and/or requests from government authorities within or outside your country of residence; (2) to protect and defend the rights or property of My Company.; (3) to enforce our Terms of Service; (4) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Company, the operation of the Service or the general public; or (5) for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate.

Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.

**Protection of Personal Information**

The Company takes precautions, including administrative, technical, and physical measures, to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

The online services offered by the Company and its affiliates use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on web pages where personal information is collected (for example, credit card and other payment information). To use these services, we recommend you use an SSL-enabled browser such as Internet Explorer, Firefox, Chrome, or Safari. Doing so protects the confidentiality of your personal information while it's transmitted over the Internet.

**Integrity and Retention of Personal Information**

The Company makes it easy for you to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date. We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

**Access to Personal Information**

If you have a Company account, you may update or correct your personal profile information at any time by visiting your account profile page.

For other personal information, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access and support so you can request that we correct the data if it is inaccurate, or delete the data if My Company. is not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes. Please contact Company's customer support here for such request. If you do not want to receive any marketing or promotional email from the Company, you can either choose the opt-out option where it is available or contact the Company's customer support here.

**Children**

The Service is not intended for or directed to persons under the age of 14. We require that use of the Service and all purchases made through it be by individuals who are 14 years of age or older. The Company does not permit registration by and will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under 14. If the Company learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under 14 we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.

**Third-Party Sites and Services**

This Privacy Policy applies only to information the Company collects about you as a user of Company Service. This policy does not apply to information about you collected by third party web sites and offerings linked to or otherwise accessible from the Company Service. The information collected or obtained by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies. Additionally, in the event you access a service using Company Service which is co-branded with a third party such third party's privacy policy, in addition to the Company Privacy Policy, may also apply.

Please note that the Company may utilize a third-party e-commerce service provider to manage its online store and the transactions related to that service. The information collected by such third-party e-commerce service provider during the transaction process is subject to their own privacy policies, and not this Privacy Policy. However, the Company will also have access to the information that you provided to such third-party e-commerce service provider.

**International Users**

Information you provide may be transferred or accessed by the Company, its agents, and affiliates around the world as described in this Privacy Policy. By using the Service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

**Privacy Questions**

If you have questions or concerns about Company's Privacy Policy, please contact us at contact.us(at)telewizjada.net

Last updated: May 03, 2013
